# Jordan Sickler

## **Software Engineer**

Tampa, FL 33626 sicklerjordan@gmail.com +1 813 724 2940

When it comes to web development I have experience working as a React.js developer. In-depth knowledge of JavaScript, CSS, HTML, and front-end languages. Knowledge of React tools including React.js, Webpack, Enzyme, Redux, and Flux. Experience with user interface design. Experience with browser-based debugging and performance testing software. Excellent troubleshooting skills. Good project management skills. Collaborates closely with product managers, designers, and other engineering teams.

Im also a experienced mobile app developer who has a track record of success creating apps that are both well-received and commercially viable. Skilled with working as a team and incorporating input into projects. Ability to always look for ways to improve upon an already existing app to keep people downloading it and enjoying it. Strong eye for detail and tenacity to never quit on something until it is absolutely perfect.

I love to hear from you. Whether you have a question or potential project — shoot me a message.

Portfolio Site: Jordansickler.com

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

# Work Experience

#### **Software Engineer**

Igas usa - Tampa, FL October 2022 to Present

- Head of the IT department responsible for redesigning and building a new website and mobile app from scratch.
- Collaborate with marketing and design teams to achieve the company's rebranding goals.

#### **UX Engineer**

Trinity Insight - Remote April 2020 to October 2022

- Designed and developed digital products, including websites and apps, using UX principles.
- Conducted technical planning, system integration, verification and validation, cost and risk analysis, supportability, and effectiveness for total systems.

#### **Web Developer**

AARO - Remote

October 2021 to December 2021

- Developed a new website using WordPress, including specific features such as contact forms, mobile responsive design, and member sign-in.
- Achieved the goal of quickly communicating AARO's mission and legitimacy in Central Texas.

# **React Native mobile developer**

FREELANCE - Tampa, FL

January 2020 to November 2021

- Built mobile apps and UI components from prototypes and wireframes using React Native.
- Wrote automated tests to ensure error-free code and performance.

## **Front End Web Developer**

1305Designs - Tampa, FL February 2018 to April 2020

- Collaborated with the team to design, structure, and implement new websites from start to finish, updated existing websites.
- Developed user-friendly architecture, provided support, and excellent customer service.
- Participated in weekly meetings with executives and supported brainstorming and generating ideas.

### **Data analyst**

Nielsen - Tampa, FL

November 2016 to March 2020

- Conducted regression analysis and provided valuable information output to clients.
- Explained study results to commercial consultants for client communication.
- Controlled project information to minimize errors and obtain high-quality results.

#### Education

#### **Bachelor's in Computer science**

University of South Florida-Main Campus - Tampa, FL 2015 to January 2019

#### High School Diploma in Basic Study

Hich School Braulio Alonso High School - Tampa, FL June 2013

#### Skills

- Computer Skills (5 years)
- Detail Oriented (5 years)
- Excel
- testing
- Powerpoint
- JavaScript
- React
- Bootstrap

- Web Development
- CSS
- Git
- SASS
- Jquery
- GitHub
- User Interface (UI)
- HTML5
- JSON
- Front-End Development
- React Native
- Redux
- APIs
- User Experience (UX)
- E-commerce (3 years)
- liquid
- Shopify
- Application Development
- kot
- Swift
- SCSS

#### Links

https://Jordansickler.com

## Assessments

# **Data Entry — Highly Proficient**

September 2019

Measures a candidate's ability to accurately input data and effectively manage databases.

Full results: Highly Proficient

# **Software developer fit — Highly Proficient**

January 2022

Measures the traits that are important for successful software developers

Full results: Highly Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.